or saleh's departure to vis fat such a
o salida de saleh a vis gorda tal xeito
powerful xeito already by the end of the month also I
potente ya para finalizar el mes además
think that this topic will be talked about
que creo que este tema van a hablar
for at least a few days I'm not going
durante al menos unos cuantos de día no
to lie okay I'm not going to play the
voy a mentir vale no voy a hacer aquí el
role here but this is to the pse or it has not
papel pero este es al pse o no me ha
caught me by surprise at all as you all
pillado de sorpresa para nada como todos
know well I get along with Dallas I don't
sabéis pues yo me llevo con dallas no
have a certain relationship with him she
tengo cierta relación con él ella me
had told me some things a
había contado algunas cosas hace ya
long time ago and I knew that it
mucho tiempo y yo sabía que solamente
was only a matter of time waiting for
era cuestión de tiempo esperar a que
Jordi to do something that would light the
jordi hiciese algo que encendiese la
fuse not at the moment the fuse would go down
mecha no en el momento descendiese la
I knew that Dallas and see float and
mecha yo sabía que dallas y ver flotar y
in this sense in this aspect already in
en este sentido en este aspecto ya en
this case I think it has been with reason
este caso yo creo que ha sido con razón
because he has a lot of things kept to himself he has kept
porque tiene muchas cosas guardadas se
quiet about many things that he hasn't
ha callado muchas cosas que no ha
said and on top of that the other one has been saying
contado y encima el otro ha ido diciendo
things out there that well they have two
por ahí cosas que bueno que tienen dos
pairs of balls but well now I'm going to
pares de [__] pero bueno ahora voy a
comment point by point what
ir comentando punto por punto lo que a
seems to me the most important most
mí me parece más importante más
relevant behind the move that just
relevante detrás movida que acaba de
happened I'm going to explain how
pasar os voy a explicar cómo se ha
that fuse was lit that has made
encendido esa mecha que ha hecho que
all this  explode I'm going to give you my
todo esto estalle os voy a dar mi
opinion and I'm going to tell you what I
opinión y os voy a comentar qué es lo
think is going to happen from
que creo que va a pasar a partir de
now
ahora pero antes de empezar con el vídeo
on but before starting with the video I'm going to talk to you about preserves and who Joseba is and that's why I said until this afternoon or five times Joseba from Carglass or I think with Joseba who is the one who fixes the windows in the advertisement well it turns out
cristales en el anuncio no pues resulta
that Jose Bas is a friend of Jorge the
ser que josé bas es un amigo de jorge el
Savage who is very angry with me
salvaje que está muy enfadado conmigo
with the author and with other youtubers because we haven't
con autor y con otras youtuber porque no
given him our own because these days
le hemos dado propia porque estos días
a clip of his has come out in some of
ha salido un clip suyo en unos vídeos
our videos and we haven't given him promos
nuestros y no le hemos dado promos
incredible suddenly this kid starts
increíble de repente este chaval empieza
bombarding us on all the
a bombardearnos en todas las redes
social networks he has posted tweets saying that you have to
sociales ha puesto tweets diciendo que
see that we have used his
hay que ver que hemos utilizado su
content without mentioning him he has sent me
contenido sin mencionarlo me ha mandado
messages he will edit he has sent messages to
mensajes editará ha mandado mensajes a
his brother to send it to me and
su hermano para que me lo mande a mí y
goes to your comments on YouTube I
va a vuestros comentarios en youtube
expand on his point not his point is that
extiendo su punto no su punto es que han
these days they have been filming on
estado rodando estos días en los canales
Salcé's channels or clips of one of his live shows and
de salcé o clips de un directo suyo y
that we have not given him credit
que no le hemos dado crédito a ver
joseba i had no [ __ ] idea of
joseba yo no tenía ni puñetera idea de
your existence i'm telling you this from the heart i
tu existencia te lo digo de corazón o
mean if i had had any idea of ​​your
sea si hubiera tenido idea de tu
existence it wouldn't have cost me a lot of work to
existencia no me hubiese costado trabajo
say hey well this is live from
decir oye pues este directo del canal de
joseba's channel but oh well don't get carried away
joseba pero bueno tampoco te rayes no
no go to all the channels to
tampoco vayas a todos los canales a
post comments it's that i want a promotion
poner comentarios es que yo quiero promo
that you haven't mentioned me and on
que no me habéis mencionado para
top of that they put my line in the description it's really annoying that you
encima ponen mi line en la descripción
come to
es que tocaste los huevos que vengas a
our channels to complain instead of
nuestros canales a quejarte en vez de
because i wanted that kid was going to
porque yo me quería que ese chaval iba a
come to tell us something defend his
venir a comentarnos algo defender a su
friend not clarify some point about
amigo no aclarara algún punto sobre
jordi that we don't know and far from
jordi que no sepamos y lejos de
worrying about what is being said
preocuparse por lo que se está diciendo
about his colleague he is worrying
de su colega él se está preocupando
because we have not given him promotion
porque no le hemos dado promoción
joseba don't get angry i already mentioned you okay
joseba no te enfades ya te menciono vale
calm me down let it happen kids i am
te me calma que pase chavalería soy
wise freedom welcome to my channel and
sabio liberdad bienvenidos a mi canal y
if this video has arrived and you
si ha llegado este vídeo y todavía no
weren't subscribed yet or didn't know me
estaba suscrito o no me conocía
please subscribe because it is
suscríbete por favor que es gratuito
totally free and we are about to reach
totalmente y estamos a punto de llegar a
300,000 subscribers it seems
los 300.000 suscriptores me parece
absolutely crazy to me it seemed absolutely
auténtica locura me pareció auténtica
crazy that they  300,000 people who
locura que hayan 300.000 personas que se
subscribe to this garbage saw subscribe to
suscriban a esta basura vio suscribir a
this channel who
este canal
knows always informed of all
vaya a saber informado siempre de todas
the controversies of the youtuber all the
las polémicas de los youtuber todos los
jumps well actually I don't know how I am
saltos bueno en realidad no sé cómo me
so surprised that there are so many people
sorprendo tanto de que haya tanta gente
subscribed to this garbage without Mauricio heretic
suscrita esta basura sin mauricio hereje
they have 2 million serious subscribers
tienen 2 millones de suscriptores graves
but well let's comment on this
pero bueno vamos a comentar esta
controversy that I find quite
polémica que a mí me parece bastante
interesting it seems to me that this one of
interesante a mí me parece que este de
salt has become quite good
sal se os ha puesto bastante bueno ya
the review is left he has uploaded a video
queda la review ha subido un vídeo en
against Jordi Guay
contra de jordi guay
Argel Savage in which he has exposed a
argel salvaje en el que ha expuesto un
lot of things that people did not know
montón de cosas que la gente no sabía
about Jordi Gual to begin with I want to
sobre jordi gual para empezar yo quiero
say that I am going to comment on the controversy I am going to
decir que voy a comentar la polémica voy
try to be as neutral as possible
a intentar ser lo más neutro posible
although I have a relationship with one and the
aunque tengo relación con uno y con el
other I don't think that really I have
otro no creo que realmente a mí jordi
ever disliked Jordi Gual more since he has
gual nunca me ha caído más ya que tiene
his voice
su voz
that has its things like we all do
que tienen sus cosas como todos los
but to me the kid
tenemos pero a mí el chaval siempre me
has always seemed very cool very nice
ha parecido muy buena onda muy simpático
Tessio talks a couple of times with the
tessio habla un par de veces con el
kid La Marga friendly and generally does
chaval la marga amable y por lo general
not usually mess with  nobody what happens is
no suele meterse con nadie lo que pasa
that on this occasion he has messed
que en esta ocasión sí que se ha metido
with dallas quite a bit but leaving aside this
con dallas bastante pero quitando este
dallas issue on other occasions I've
tema de dallas en otras ocasiones lo
seen it and he enjoys messing with no one and
visto y disfrutar de meterse con nadie y
looking for controversy as well as for
buscar polémica así como que
free in fact I've always seen him have
gratuitamente de hecho le visto siempre
a good vibe with all the youtubers I don't
un buen rollo con todos los youtuber no
know why well I imagine because he's
sé por qué bueno me imagino porque la
having a hard time I imagine it's
pasando con tablas me imagino que será
because he gets together with certain friends and
por juntarse con ciertas amistades y
lets himself go I don't know let's talk about it
dejarse llevar no lo sé vamos a hablarlo
in this video the only thing that yes from my
en este vídeo lo único que sí desde mi
point of view is what the
punto de vista es lo que viene siendo el
content is jordi gual he has messed up
contenido jordi gual él ha metido la
well to me it really seemed like
pata bueno a mí realmente me ha parecido
two occasions in which jordi gual has
dos ocasiones en las que jordi gual ha
made two pathetic videos one of them
hecho dos vídeos patéticos uno de ellos
was the video he made about the
fue el vídeo que hizo sobre el incendio
amazon fire which I think was a
de la amazona que me parece que fue un
video that he made completely
vídeo que hizo completamente
uninformed or rather saying a lot of
desinformado o sea diciendo un montón de
nonsense that he hadn't even
tonterías que ni siquiera se había
stopped to get a little bit of information
parado a [__] un poquito de información
and soaking it up was a bit to make a
y empaparse era un poco para hacer un
decent video like for example the one he
vídeo en condiciones como por ejemplo el
made precisely 20 [ __ ]
que hizo darlas precisamente 20 jodidos
days that the amazon is in a
días que la amazona se está en una
crisis  impressive incendiary like I've
crisis incendiaria impresionante como
never had before
nunca jamás había tenido
host how strong and like I've never
[__] qué fuerte y como nunca más había
had an incredible fire in the
tenido un incendio increíble en las
Amazon again I'm going to publish it on instagram
amazonas voy a publicarlo en instagram
quickly to save them but one
rápidamente para salvarlas pero un
moment before you rush
momento antes de que te precipites
remember that I might be a
recordad que yo igual es un progre de
textbook progressive and that logically not
manual y que lógicamente no han pasado
even two minutes have passed and he has already told you several
ni dos minutos y ya os ha dicho varias
lies yes also accompanied with a
mentiras si además acompañado con un
tone of the end of the world all very progressive
tono de fin del mundo todo muy progre
let's review Jordi's lies the
vamos a repasar las mentiras de jordi la
first of all no it is not a fire
primera de todas no no es un incendio
like the Amazon has never had before
como nunca más había tenido el amazonas
in reality according to the 'New York Times'
en realidad según el 'new york times'
team of being a graph with all the
equipo de ser un gráfico con todos los
fires that the Amazon has had
incendios que ha tenido el amazonas
for many years the darkest line
durante muchos años la línea más oscura
the black one is from the year 2019 and as you can see it does not
la negra es del año 2019 y como veis no
exceed the red lines which are from the
supera las líneas rojas que son de los
previous years from 2010 to 2018 but
anteriores años del 2010 al 2018 pero es
if you look there are some gray lines
que si os fijáis hay unas líneas gris
those are from the year I have the cheat sheet here
esas son del año tengo aquí la chuleta
2003 to 2010 and as you can see they
2003 al 2010 y como veis superan por
far exceed 2019
mucho al 2019
a video that was for  throw myself on the floor and
un vídeo que fue para tirarme al suelo y
do the croquette was the video that he made
hacer la croqueta fue el vídeo que hizo
about Michael Jackson talking about the
sobre michael jackson hablando sobre el
documentary that came out about Michael Jackson which
documental que salió de michael jackson
was a documentary that I made two
que era un documental que yo hice dos
videos on this channel I think that on the
vídeos en este canal creo que en el
secondary channel I was also talking
canal secundario también estuve hablando
about that documentary Living Neverland and it is
de ese documental living neverland y es
a documentary that is absolutely false it
un documental que es absolutamente falso
is half of a documentary all of the
es una mitad de documental todas las
information that is given is
informaciones que se dan están
manipulated with the intention of defaming
manipuladas con la intención de difamar
and tarnishing the image of Michael Jackson and
y manchar la imagen de michael jackson y
with the intention of making money from a
con la intención de hacer dinero de una
totally false controversy okay here we
polémica totalmente falsa vale aquí le
ask you a tremendous contradiction and that is that
pidamos una contradicción tremenda y es
James's mother in the documentary
que la madre de james en el documental
we hear her say that when Michael
la escuchamos decir que cuando michael
Jackson died she began to dance with
jackson murió ella se puso a bailar de
happiness celebrating that no
felicidad celebrando que irá ningún niño
more children would suffer because there is a
más iba a sufrir porque hay una
contradiction because supposedly James
contradicción porque supuestamente james
realized and realized that
se dio cuenta y cayó en la cuenta de que
Michael Jackson abused him now
michael jackson abusó de él ahora hace
five years ago when Michael Jackson died
cinco años cuando michael jackson murió
he had not yet realized according to
él todavía no se había dado cuenta según
him another very powerful contradiction in
él otra contradicción muy potente en
this interview where he recognizes well he
esta entrevista donde reconoce bueno le
asks him if they knew each other as children
pregunta que si se conocieron de pequeño
and they say no way they say that he saw
y ellos dicen que no way dicen que vio a
James in the  Pepsi ad but they didn't
james en el anuncio de pepsi pero que no
know each other in person when months
se conocían en persona cuando meses más
later after the premiere of Living
tarde después del estreno de living
Neverland in the interview with Oprah he
neverland en la entrevista con oprah
says
dice
that they did meet when little
que sí que se conocieron cuando pequeños
friends you have to take the
amigos hay que llevarse las preguntas
most studied questions because lies have
más estudiadas que las mentiras tienen
very short legs I feel very bad
las patas muy cortas me siento muy mal
that Jordi Guay gave happiness to that
que jordi guay le diese felicidad a ese
documentary and it gave me the
documental y es que me dio la impresión
total impression well it gave me the impression he
total bueno me dio la impresión nos
totally showed us that he simply
demostró totalmente que simplemente se
watched the documentary he didn't even stop to
vio el documental ni siquiera se paró a
think and check the arguments
pensar y a comprobar los argumentos que
given in that documentary and he doesn't inform himself
daban en ese documental y no se informa
that much he had no idea what he
una tanto no tenía ni idea de lo que
was talking about and since the documentary was
estaba hablando y como el documental era
viral the video was made quickly and come on
viral se hizo el vídeo rapidito y venga
here more without informing himself absolutely
para acá más sin informarse una absoluta
but I promise the video he made about
pero lo prometo el vídeo que hizo sobre
Living Neverland pisses me
el living neverland me cabreo que te
off because it's a video that has 3 or 4
caga porque es un vídeo que tienen 3 o 4
million views and a video that
millones de visitas y un vídeo que
misinforms a lot of people and he
desinforma un montón a la gente y
should use his influence to
debería aprovechar su influencia para
give truthful information informed it doesn't
dar información verídica informados no
cost anything ces google
cuesta nada ces google
and in five or ten minutes you have
y en cinco o diez minutos tienes
information to talk about how many of you
información para hablar de cómo muchos
will remember Dallas and Jordi Guay  they have
recordaréis dallas y jordi gual de hace
n't gotten along for a long time they
mucho tiempo no se llevan bien ellos
call it has faced many years and
llaman ha enfrentado bastantes años y en
especially people believe that all this
especial la gente se cree que toda esta
controversy began with a video that
polémica comenzó con un vídeo que le
made him boast that was called Jordi White the
hizo gala que se llamaba jordi white el
planet of YouTube according to people and
planeta de youtube según la gente y
according to what people believe
según se cree la gente
this video is the one that would start the
este vídeo es el que iniciaría la
enmity between all of them people were
enemistad entre todos la gente estaba
wrong about this and Jordi Güell has been
equivocada con esto y jordi güell se lo
very quiet about it but really the
tiene muy calladito pero realmente la
enmity that Dallas has with Jordi
enemistad que tiene dallas con jordi
Gual comes from things that happened in
gual viene por cosas que pasaron en la
private apparently according to what he tells us
intimidad por lo visto según nos cuenta
in this video before that criticism it
él en este vídeo antes de esa crítica os
will surprise you but I hadn't seen
va a sorprender pero no me había visto
that video yet or if I saw it in its
ese vídeo todavía o si me lo vi en su
day I don't remember but I saw it
día no me acuerdo pero me lo he visto
today calmly analyzing everything I've
hoy tranquilamente analizándolo todo el
seen there carefully to have an
visto hay detenidamente para tener una
opinion of what that video is like and say it
opinión de cómo es ese vídeo y decir
really was as serious as people
realmente era tan grave como la gente lo
painted it not because let's remember that Win
pintaba no porque recordemos que win
Michu even took this video out in the
michu este vídeo incluso lo sacó en el
Treasury the review as if it were a
hacienda la review como si fuese un
good video a super destructive video
vídeo bueno un vídeo súper destructivo
that sent Jordi White's ex-girlfriend to be harassed  the
que mandaba a acosar a la exnovia de
hard part of this video was not
jordi white o duro de este vídeo no fue
that he hurt jordi no the hard part
que le hiciese daño a jordi no lo duro
of this video was that he hurt a
de este vídeo fue que le hizo daño a un
third party natalie for all the sticks
tercero a natalie para todos los palitos
at that time they went after that
en aquel entonces se lanzaron a por esa
girl to the point that she
chavala hasta el punto de que ella
also suffered harassment in the streets and
también sufrió acoso en las calles y
michu begins to affirm that for natalie for
michu se pone afirmar que a natalie para
the thing on the street after
la cosa por la calle después del vídeo
dalt's video she has done the same thing that they
de dalt ha hecho lo mismo que se
started to say about mieres and ingrid it
pusieron a decir de mieres y de ingrid
's not like they wanted to make
no es como que querían hacer
an image of dallas that every time she
una imagen de dallas que cada vez que le
makes a video to someone especially if it is
hace un vídeo a alguien sobre todo si es
a woman of course all the people on the
una mujer claro toda la gente por la
street or in other words the girls would not be
calle o sea las chavalas ya no iba a
able to go out on the street because
poder salir a la calle porque todo el
everyone harassed her and that is something that does
mundo la acosaba y es una cosa que a mí
not fit me because according to the argument
no me cuadra porque según el argumento
of these people also all of
de esta gente también todos los
dallas' followers were small children
seguidores de dallas eran niños pequeños
who allowed themselves to be manipulated so I can't
que se dejaban manipular entonces no me
imagine this girl walking down the
imagino yo a esta chica yendo por la
street and four 13 year old brats
calle y cuatro niñatos de 13 años
harassing her very good and less having
acosando la muy bueno y menos teniendo
jordi gual calavera not as a boyfriend who
jordi gual calavera no de novio que te
grabs you does you like that  they rack their brains
coge te hace así te estrujan la cabeza
this victimhood doesn't make any sense anymore
ya no tiene sentido este victimismo
in fact as was being said
ninguno de hecho como se estaba diciendo
I watched the Dallas video
me he visto el vídeo de dallas
again the old video and he doesn't mess
otra vez el vídeo antiguo y no se mete
with her the disgusting comments on
con ella los comentarios asquerosos en
twitter and this year making
el twitter y este año hacer comentarios
literal comments in videos saying watch what he
literales en vídeos diciendo ojo lo que
said honey the one between your
dijo tesoro el que tiene entre las
legs referring to one of
piernas refiriéndose a una de las
this year's contestants very well that is a
concursantes de este año muy bien eso es
very adult very mature attitude I'm sure
una actitud muy adulta muy madura seguro
your girlfriend was really amused to see
que a tu novia le hizo mucha gracia ver
that and meanwhile you find
eso y mientras tanto te la encuentras a
her on her twitter posting thousands of
ella en su twitter publicando miles de
photos of him and saying things like he's the
fotos de él y diciendo cosas como es el
love of my life or he's the perfect guy or I
amor de mi vida o es el chico perfecto o
love my boyfriend things are very
amo a mi novio la cosa está muy
very balanced do you think that's
muy balanceada eso os parece que está
okay for a relationship because it doesn't seem like it to me
bien para una relación porque a mí no me
definitely if I had to
lo parece definitivamente si tuviera que
choose the example of a healthy
escoger el ejemplo de una relación sana
adult relationship I doubt very much that I would ever choose this one
y adulta dudo mucho que jamás escogiera
where she is with his victim
está donde ella está con la víctima de
while he makes videos of photos and
él mientras él hace vídeos de fotos y
videos masturbating of other girls who
videos masturbándose de otras tías que
also want to [ __ ] him that's what you
además se lo quieren [__] lo es lo que
do to girls nobody can take away from you
las hechos a chavalas no te lo quita
given let's see I'm going to  give my
nadie dadas a ver os voy a dar mi
opinion on that video from 2015 that I just
opinión sobre ese vídeo del año 2015 que
saw today, honestly
me lo acabo de ver hoy a mí sinceramente
what would offend me if it were Jordi Wild
lo que me ofendería si fuese jordi wild
and what I think could have
y lo que yo creo que él ha podido
offended him about that video is the title that
ofender de ese vídeo es el título que se
uses the word prostate. I understand
utilice la palabra próstata yo entiendo
that Darla when he gave the video this title
que darla cuando le puso este título al
when during the video he calls it
vídeo cuando durante el vídeo le llama
prostate he didn't mean to give it its
próstata no quiso darle su significado
literal meaning because the literal meaning is
literal porque significado literal está
related to prostitution
relacionado con la prostitución
literally, that is, with prostitutes. I
literalmente o sea con prostitutas yo
understand that Darla what he wants to do
entiendo que darán lo que quiere hacer
is like a kind of comparison, not
es como una especie de comparación no
like finding some kind of similarity
como encontrar algún tipo de similitud
between what Jordi does and a prostate in the
entre lo que hace jordi y un próstata de
same way, I think that well he decided to
igual forma yo creo que bueno decidió
leave Jordi Gual putting me in his place,
fuera jordi gual poniéndome en su lugar
that word. The fact that they used
a mí esa palabra a mí que se me ponga
that title could offend me. So
ese título pues me puede ofender
I think that what pissed Jordi Wild off
entonces yo creo que a jordi guay lo que
and what offended him was what
le cabreo y lo que le ofendió fue lo que
the title is
viene siendo el título del
because then really what the
porque luego realmente lo que es el
rest of the criticism is is
resto de la crítica es una crítica
constructive criticism, not
constructiva no es una crítica
destructive criticism. It is also a criticism in
destructiva además es una crítica en la
which he is talking and giving his opinion on
que está hablando y opinando de cosas
real things that are  happening on his channel at
reales que están pasando en su canal en
no time does he disrespect
ningún momento le falta el respeto ni a
him or Natalie for the criticisms he
él ni a natalie para las críticas que le
makes it would be divided into two parts in the
hace se dividiría en dos partes en la
first part he criticizes the contest is
primera parte critica el concurso esté
good criticism explains a little of what
bueno crítica explica un poco de lo que
the contest is about this girlfriend of the
trata el concurso este de la novia del
channel that a contest almost to Jordi Gual
canal que un concurso casi a jordi gual
so that the girls could send him
para para que las chicas le mandasen
photos they were generally sexy photos and
fotos por lo general eran fotos sexys y
I am still there because he judged her if they were
yo sigo ahí pues la juzgaba si estaba
good and not so good and he wanted them
buenas y no tan buenas y se las quería
without another it would be in the end to end up
sin otra sería para el final acabar
having a relationship with the winner
teniendo una relación con la ganadora
of the contest that I do not know if he
del concurso que yo no sé si esto lo
had planned this or not the thing changes the
tenía el planeado o no la cosa cambie la
idea of ​​the contest well it may seem
idea del concurso bueno puede parecer
sexist misogynistic that July to
machista misógino que se julio a las
women that they are treated as an object that is
mujeres que se les trate como objeto que
caused if and that it seems to me that
se le cause if y que a mí me parece que
while the candidates know what they
mientras que las candidatas sepan a lo
are exposing themselves to, that is to say that
que se están exponiendo es decir que
they are volunteers to present themselves to
ellas son voluntarias de presentarse a
that contest so that Jordi judges her
ese concurso para que jordi la juzgue
say if she is good and not so good and is
diga si está buenas y no tan buenas y es
ugly and he takes them if not he takes it it
fea y se las lleva si no se lo lleva a
seems to me that as long as the girls
mí me parece que mientras que las chicas
know what they are exposing themselves to and
sepan a lo que se están exponiendo y
They voluntarily participate it
ellas voluntariamente participen
seems like there is no problem other than
parece que no hay ningún problema aparte
that it may seem like sexism to us or
de que nos pueda parecer machismo o lo
whatever we want but at the end of the day it
que queramos pero al fin y al cabo no
is not forcing anyone to participate in
está obligando a nadie a participar en
this contest equally we are
este concurso igualmente estamos
talking about 2015 or that we are talking about the
hablando de 2015 o que estamos hablando
year 2015 in which we had
del año 2015 en el que teníamos
normalized other things that maybe today are
normalizadas otras cosas que tal vez hoy
not these seeds of the contest seem
no estas semillas del concurso me parece
good to me what I do agree with
bien lo que sí que estoy de acuerdo en
Dallas' criticism is that I would not
la crítica de dallas es en que yo no
rate my girlfriend anymore, I mean
calificaría ya a mi novia o sea ya una
once I have a partner I would not use her
vez teniendo pareja no la utilizaría
to put her tits in a thumbnail
para poner sus tetas en una miniatura
to expose her segment in my videos
para exponerla segmente en mis vídeos
to get pastor's attention because
para llamar la atención de pastor porque
hey call me old fashioned call me sexist
oye llamarme antiguo llamarme machista
call me whatever you want I know that there will be
llamarme lo que queráis yo sé que habrá
people who do not like it anymore because it
gente a la que no le parezca más porque
will be good for them as long as the girl
le irá bueno mientras que la chica esté
agrees they can do whatever she wants let her
de acuerdo pueden hacer lo que quiera
use her body do whatever she wants
que utilice su cuerpo que haga lo que le
but I sincerely as a
dé la gana pero yo sinceramente como
boyfriend I would not do it I prefer to make
novio pues no lo haría yo prefiero hacer
the payment with my girlfriend I do not let
la paga con mi novia yo no que se la
others do it to me sincerely
hagan los demás a mí sinceramente el
using your partner in that way does not
utilizar a tu pareja de ese modo pues no
seem right to me listen in my opinion  you
me parece oye en mi opinión a usted en
were good to me in another way but I don't
otra era bueno conmigo eso pero yo no
use my partner that way and
utilizo a mi pareja de esa forma y ya
then the fact that the following year you do
luego el hecho de que haga al año
the
siguiente otra vez el concurso de la
channel's girlfriend contest again having a partner and
novia del canal teniendo pareja y otra
again a bunch of girls sending pictures
vez un montón de tías mandando de fotos
special playing if she could if she couldn't, well, it
especial jugando si se la podía si no se
seems to me a lack of respect
pues a mí me parece una falta de respeto
to your partner, no, it seems to me that you
a tu pareja no a mí me parece que tú
can have an opinion if a pretty girl, if not
puedes opinar si una chica guapa sino
pretty, you can have a platonic love that
guapa puedes tener un amor platónico que
is famous, an actress that you have
sea una famosa una actriz que te haya
liked your whole life but that you
gustado de toda la vida pero que te
put your followers and they
pongas con tus seguidoras a que te
send you those types of photos and you evaluate them, it
manden ese tipo de fotos y tú evaluarlas
gives me the feeling that you
a mí me da la sensación de que tú la
ate your head, the girl, that the girl
comió la cabeza la chica que la chica
is super in love with you and you have
está súper enamorada de ti y tú le has
told her, hey, these jobs, these
dicho oye que estos trabajos estos
shows in her fiction, this is not
espectáculos en su ficción esto no es de
real, let me do it, you can't
verdad déjame lo hace no me lo puedes
forbid me because these jobs and you have, this
prohibir porque estos trabajos y tú has
is my job, anything that,
está mi trabajo cualquier cosa eso
also it seems that after the Dallas video,
además parece ser que después del vídeo
Natalie pasta or putting up some other
natalie pasta o poniendo algún que otro
tweet and in this one, I don't know if you
tweet y en este no sé si ustedes
understand the reference the same as I do, the
entender la referencia igual que yo la
tip of the iceberg  as they say in
punta del iceberg como bien le dicen en
the comments, the one who understood,
los comentarios el que entendió lo
understood it, well that's what I'm telling you, what
entendió bueno es lo que os digo lo que
the criticism is, it's an opinion,
viene siendo la crítica es una opinión
well there will be people who
que bueno habrá gente que esté de
agree and people who don't, but it's an
acuerdo y gente que no pero es una
opinion based on things from his channel, it's not
opinión basada en cosas de su canal no
based on personal things as they have
está basada en cosas personales como
always wanted to make it seem and it is a
siempre han querido hacer ver y es una
criticism made from hate, if you
crítica hecha desde el odio es que si tú
have made a spectacle of your
has hecho un espectáculo de tu relación
romantic relationship, don't stay there, criticize
sentimental no te quedes cañas críticas
about that, it becomes something that
sobre eso se convierte en una cosa que
is not personal,
no es personal
apart from the 30 that I understand
aparte de los 30 que yo entiendo que se
can be offended by
puede ofender por
adjective, it seems to me that with that perhaps it
adjetivo me parece que con eso quizás se
snuck in a little, the only thing I didn't
coló un poco lo único que no me ha
like about that criticism is that Dallas
gustado de esa crítica es que dallas
says something like that whoever has
dice algo así como que el que tiene
many followers who are small, they
muchos seguidores que son pequeños que
are very young and impressionable and you
son muy jóvenes e influenciables y no
are not giving them the best example because it
les estás dando el mejor ejemplo porque
will be an argument that they have used
será un argumento que han utilizado
both with me and with the Dalai himself and
tanto conmigo como con el propio dalai y
an argument that we have denied a
un argumento que hemos desmentido un
lot of times because we are not
montón de veces porque nosotros no somos
responsible and we are teachers and parents
responsables y somos profesores y padres
of the people who see us, our content
de la gente que nos ve nuestro contenido
is not for children but according to children
no es para niños sino según niños
the problem is with their parents who let them
el problema de sus padres que les dejen
be on the internet, in fact I  I'm
estar en internet de hecho yo estoy
absolutely sure that Dallas would
totalmente seguro que dallas a día de
n't use that inferior argument today. I
hoy no utilizaría ese argumento inferior
agree with him. The thing is that over
acuerdo con él la cosa es que con el
time, both Jordi Gual and some of
tiempo tanto jordi gual como algunos de
his friends have been forming the
sus amiguitos han estado formando la
opinion in people that it was Dallas
opinión en la gente de que fue dallas el
who attacked first with this
que atacó primero con este vídeo tan
offensive video that got into his
ofensivo que se metía en su vida
personal life and attacked his girlfriend. They
personal y atacaba a su novia y los
want to make him look like a
quieren poner encima como una persona
spiteful person because they blame him for
rencorosa porque le echan la culpa al
having made this criticism because Dallas
haberle hecho esta crítica a que dallas
first asked Jordi
primero le pidió colaboración a jordi
Gual for collaboration and he rejected it. If I think about it
gual y éste se la rechazó si lo pensaré
today, this argument is totally
hoy en día este argumento es totalmente
invalid and ridiculous, not only because of the
inválido y ridículo no sólo por las
new information that Dallas has just released,
nuevas informaciones que acaba de soltar
but also because the criticism
dallas sino además porque en la crítica
is based on machismo and things about
se basa en el machismo y cosas
women. Jordi Gual in the past and
las mujeres jordi gual en el pasado y el
Jordi White himself on many
propio jordi white en muchísimas
occasions today has recognized that he
ocasiones hoy en día ha reconocido
regrets such acts. I
arrepentirse de tales actos y yo
recognize that I had many
reconozco que tuve muchos
behaviors that today
comportamientos que hoy en día pues no
are not acceptable and that is a reality. I'm
son aceptables y eso es una realidad ya
not talking about YouTube laws, anal or
no hablo de leyes de youtube de anal o
image quality, quality of  do
de calidad de imagen de calidad de
it seeing the behavior
hacerlo viendo el comportamiento sobre
especially towards the subject women because
todo hacia el tema mujeres pues que hoy
today the world has changed a
en día el mundo ha cambiado una
lot, I myself have changed
barbaridad yo mismo he cambiado
normality and you do two things that is that
normalidad y haces dos cosas que es que
I myself already feel bad also that
yo mismo ya me siento mal además tampoco
we have to have happened to
que nos tengamos que haya pasado para
find her Jordi having that attitude
encontrarla jordi teniendo esa actitud
true this video without animals a
verdad este vídeo sin animales hace un
couple of years ago
par de años
as published today I have not flirted or
como publica hoy no he ligado o bien
money no matter how it is always nice
dinero no sea como sea siempre bonito
that girls say things
que digan cosas las chicas
as you already know if you have seen the
como ya sabéis si habéis visto el vídeo
Dallas video but now we will talk about it
de dallas pero ahora hablaremos de eso
more
más en profundidad existía una cosa que
in depth there was something that had happened in the private sphere and that gives the well at the time he did not want to put he wanted to criticize them only with the things that were already public but there was one more thing that Dallas had saved against Jordi Wild and that is that on one
en contra jordi wild y es que en una
occasion he asked on his ex girlfriend's cell phone
ocasión pidió en el móvil de su ex novia
on Mieres' cell phone to Jordi while
en el móvil de mieres a jordi while
sending him all kinds of suggestive messages and he
mandándole mensaje toas y sugerente e
even says that he sent him nudes if this
incluso dice que le mandaba nude si este
man Jordi like who right now is
señor jordi gual que ahora mismo tiene
35 years old about to turn 36 when you were
35 tacos a punto de los 36 cuando tenías
30 years old
30 años
jordi wild or almost 30 you dedicated yourself to
jordi wild o casi 30 te dedicaste a
sending [ __ ] light to my ex when we
mandarle puñeteros luz a mi ex cuando
were together when she was 16
estábamos juntos cuando ella tenía 16
years old a man of 30 years old you know well I
años un señor de 30 tacos ya sabéis pues
have a certain relationship with so and so there are
yo tengo cierta relación con tal hay
some things we have talked about and this thing about her
algunas cosas la hemos hablado y esto de
asking for these messages
que pidió estos mensajes ya me lo había
he had already told me a while ago and the truth is I was
contado él hace tiempo y la verdad me
quite surprised that at the time he didn't
sorprendió bastante que en su momento no
put them going when all he
les pusiese iba cuando todo él
was saying how good it was that he was
estaba diciendo que qué bueno que él se
looking for trouble with jordi white
buscaba el problema con jordi white
for free that jordi had never
gratuitamente que jordi nunca le había
done anything to him and such and it seems to me it seems
hecho nada y tal y me parece me parece
very strong sincerely it seems
muy fuerte sinceramente me parece
very strong there are no two or three things that
fortísimo no hay dos o tres cosas que me
surprise me about this one is that jordi wild
sorprenden de esto una es que jordi wild
at the moment that the whole thing happened
en el momento que pasó toda la movida
is the wind michu de mier and so on he
está the wind michu de mier y demás te
started using the ally argument that
puso a utilizar el argumento aliado de
I will do it it was only a small line
que me haré era sólo una línea pequeña
then the girls were left that she was a
después quedaron las niñas que era una
little girl sachs what are you telling me at
niña pequeña sachs que me estás contando
18 years old hit on her flying stem she was
con 18 años meterle stem voladora era
only a little girl but you really
sólo una niña pequeña pero tú bien que
tried to flirt with her no according to she doesn't
intentaba ligar con ella no según no
tell anything besides there is a huge
cuenta nada además de que hay muchísima
age difference because  Jordi Gual is
diferencia de edad porque jordi gual
one year older than me, he should be
tiene un año más que yo él tiene que
36 this year, and if we're
cumplir este año los 36 y si estamos
talking about 2014, Jordi
hablando que esto fue en el 2014 jordi
Gual would be 13 and I'd be around
gual tendría 13 años y me haré rondaría
16. You may think she's cute, you may
los 16 te puede parecer mona te puede
think she's pretty, but that's enough for
parecer guapa pero tanto como para
a 30-year-old guy to like you. It's
gustarte ya a un tío de 30 años lo
normal for him to like more mature
normal es que le guste más maduritas más
women, just like you might be attracted to a
mujeres tal como te puede atraer una
girl so young, too young. The
niña tan joven tan demasiado joven es la
truth is that at 30, I can't imagine myself
verdad que yo con 30 años no me imagino
taking a 16-year-old girl to a
con una chica de 16 llevándola a un
restaurant and what kind of conversations
restaurante y qué tipo de conversaciones
to have. And not only that, but
de tener y ya no solamente eso sino que
physically you may not think she's pretty or
físicamente no te puede parecer guapa
cute or anything, but from there to being
linda y demás pero de ahí a que te
attracted to her right now is weird. And then the
atraiga actualmente es raro y luego lo
other thing that Dallas has revealed is the fact
otro que ha desvelado dallas es el hecho
that he not only knows about the
de que no solamente sabe de las
conversations he had with Mieres,
conversaciones que él mantuvo con mieres
but he also has another friend who's also
sino que además tiene otra amiga también
quite young, with whom he also had
bastante joven con la que también tuvo
certain risqué conversations.
ciertas conversaciones subidas de tono
My ex wasn't the only one, she wasn't the only
mi ex no fue la única no fue la única
girl you sent things to, I have
chavala a la que mandaste cosas tengo
another friend who is actually  a friend of mine and
otra amiga que de hecho es amiga mía y
from icsid a while ago now she
del icsid hace un tiempo que ahora mismo
's 20 years old with this
a día de hoy tiene 20 años con esta
friend jordi when she was already 15 she had it
amiga jordi cuando ya tenía 15 tuvo a
through your skype jordi mystery you
través de tu skype jordi misterio te
used to send her stupid things you at
dedicabas a mandarle cosas de baboso tú
30 years old at thirty something years old it
con 30 tacos con treinta y pico tacos
was her mother who blocked
fue la madre de ella quien te bloqueó a
you on skype and this makes me really angry
ti de skype y esto me da muchísima rabia
okay after knowing this I find it
vale después de saber esto me parece
quite ironic that jordi while
bastante irónico que jordi while hace
only seven hours ago put out a tweet
solamente siete horas ha puesto un tweet
saying this not about the bow tie no what was
diciendo esto no lo de pajarita no cuál
the trigger for dallas to
ha sido el detonante para que dallas de
suddenly make this video well the
repente le haga este vídeo bien pues el
trigger is that there are many people who won't
detonante que hay mucha gente que no lo
know and will think that dallas suddenly came out
sabrá y se pensará que dallas de repente
of nowhere making this election video
ha salido de la nada haciendo este vídeo
that a girl made a series of
que una chica hizo una serie de
compilations of all the things that
recopilaciones de todas las cosas que
jordi white has been saying over
está diciendo jordi white a lo largo de
the last few years about dallas from that
los últimos años sobre dallas de esa
compilation joint aute we made
recopilación joint aute nos hemos sacado
some videos in the end all those things
unos vídeos al final todas esas cosas
have reached dallas it pisses you off
han llegado a dallas te dan infla los
and he decided to answer the
[__] y ha decidido responder la
truth that for three years jordi  while
verdad que durante tres años jordi while
has gone too far with dallas after
se ha pasado bastante con dallas tras
this response he has looked for it but it is done with
esta respuesta se la ha buscado pero a
force that there will be many people who
pulso se hace que habrá mucha gente que
cenima nity that this video has no to do
ensima nidad que este vídeo pues no ha
but it seems to me that it
venido a cuento pero a mí me parece que
is quite justified after breaking
está bastante justificado después partir
dallas' legs to see when
las piernas a dallas a ver cuando está
the mousse is and for having energy but they would not
la mousse y por poseer energía pero no
do it
lo harían
well no I am not going to say that in video I will
bueno no no voy a decir que en vídeo
never say that he is worth what he is on twitter
nunca diré que vale lo que es en twitter
neither would he mince a hair with a knife what
tampoco se cortaba un pelo a cuchillo lo
I hallucinate is that youtube allows
que alucino es que youtube permita a
someone like dallas to continue on the
alguien como dallas seguir en la
platform as if nothing happened I hope that one
plataforma como si nada espero que algún
day things will change
día cambien las cosas
youtube has been seeming like
youtube me estaba apareciendo
[ __ ] to me lately but if dallas
últimamente una [__] pero si dallas
ends up disappearing I think I will start to
acaba desapareciendo creo que empezaré a
look at it with good eyes again like this and do
mirarlo con buenos ojos de nuevo así y
you remember the tweet I posted before I have
os acordáis del tuiteo puse antes he
posted two or three times I don't even know in which
puesto dos o tres veces ya ni lo sé en
dallas announced
el que dallas anunciaba
jordi that he never ended up coming out and those
jordi que nunca terminó saliendo y esos
clown emoticons well it comes from
emoticonos de payasito pues viene por
this and the first of the two is defined
esto y el primero de los dos se define
when I don't tell you Mr. Jordi while
cuando no te lo digo señor jordi while
retweeted the following  It turns out that a
retuiteó lo siguiente resulta ser que un
user said about the review clown and I
usuario dijo de la review payaso y yo
draw retweeted but you didn't say that you're not
dibujo retuiteó pero tú no decías que no
going to get involved anymore Jordi quoted
te vas a meter más por medio jordi citó
there if they can get you the
ahí si es que te pueden te pueden las
desire can get you there he had the dagger hito clarified
ganas tenía ahí el puñal hito aclarado
he's done and I don't want to talk about the
el ya está y no quiero hablar más del
subject anymore not on twitter or on videos or
tema ni por twitter ni por vídeos ni
much less so let him win and well
mucho menos o sea que se gane él y bueno
in a way I could justify it to
en cierto modo yo lo podría justificar a
Jordi I could put myself in his shoes there's no need to
jordi me podría poner en su piel no hay
justify it a little in the case that there
justificarle un poco en el caso de que
were only clicks and extracts of
solamente existiesen clic y extractos de
live shows and videos that were old
directos y vídeos que fuesen antiguos
today from the time of 2017 and beyond
hoy de la época de 2017 y más allá
because back then let's be honest
porque en aquel entonces seamos sinceros
a lot of people were wrong about
muchísima gente nos equivocamos con
Dallas we believed the things that
dallas nos creíamos las cosas que se
were said about him but it turns out that
decían de él pero es que resulta ser que
among all those clicks he also puts
entre todos esos clic también pone
some that are new like this one well
algunos que son nuevos como por ejemplo
look then at zero I have no
éste pues mira entonces en cero no tengo
[ __ ] idea the truth is the truth whether they are
ni [__] idea la verdad es la verdad sean
or not I know it is no no I don't know it's the only thing I
o no se es no no no sé es lo único que
know it's something with two that there was a problem
sé es algo con dos que hubo follón
because I saw some prose video and to
porque veía algún vídeo de prosa y para
give it up but no  I came in I knew the
dar hasta el pero no entré sabía el
title
título
I think it's pretty calm the
yo creo que está bastante tranquila la
story will last if he wins his thing and
historia que dure si gana lo suyo y
until but right now I don't have it I lost I
hasta pero ahora mismo no lo tengo perdí
lost totally and according to what he says it's not an
perdí total y según comenta no es una
evasion since the slightest thing he says something
evasiva ya que a la mínima que dice algo
about Dallas he shits on your chest if he has to
de dallas se caga en tu pechito si tiene
say something he says it but apparently it's
que decir algo lo dice pero por lo visto
true he doesn't know anything
es cierto no sabe nada
[Music]
[Música]
Díaz [ __ ] idea what are you telling me a few
díaz [__] idea que me dices hace unos
years ago I read it club come on I'm going to shoot him
años la leo club vamos lo voy a pegar un
because right now what is
tiro que ahora mismo lo que es
totally recent because he mentions the
totalmente reciente porque menciona las
stuff about pieces of Dallas that they want me to
movidas de trozos de dallas que quieren
tell you it seems to me that he goes too far
que os diga me parece que se pasa mucho
with what he says no I don't know it seems to me that it
con lo que dice no no sé me parece que
is like some kind of pretty
es como una especie de amenaza bastante
explicit threat from my point of view I don't know
explícita desde mi punto de vista no sé
if it could be considered as such but to
si podría considerarse como tal pero a
me it doesn't seem to be in good taste at
mí no me parece buen gusto para nada por
least and the thing is that in this
lo menos y la cosa es que en este
aspect I have been disappointed by Jordi because
aspecto me ha decepcionado jordi porque
I have always thought when I spoke
yo siempre he pensado cuando lo hablaba
to Dallas not the whole thing about what
con dallas no todo el tema este de lo
happened to him with Jordi in the past and all
que le pasó con jordi en el pasado y tal
and also this can be confirmed by the fact that
y además esto lo puede confirmar el que
I have said it to him personally that
yo se lo he dicho a él personalmente que
I trusted
yo confiaba
that Jordi if at some point he had to
en que jordi si en algún momento tuviese
talk about Dallas again he would
que volver a hablar de dallas se
apologize he would have no problem
disculparía no tendría ningún problema
admitting that he was wrong in the
en reconocer que estuvo equivocado en el
past that many of us think badly of
pasado que mucha gente pensamos mal de
Dallas back then we didn't write
dallas en aquel entonces no escribimos
the words of Wing Michu but if
las palabras del wing michu pero que si
today the subject of talking
hoy en día le saliese el tema de hablar
about Dallas came up I was almost sure thank
de dallas yo estaba casi seguro menos
goodness I didn't bet a hand because I would have
mal que no me aposté una mano porque lo
lost I was almost sure
hubiera perdido yo estaba casi seguro de
that Jordi would have no problem
que jordi no tendría problema en
rectifying and far from that what I've
rectificar y lejos de eso lo que lo he
seen him say in these clicks that he posts is that well
visto decir en estos clic que pone es
okay now Dallas is calm that it
que bueno que vale que ahora dallas está
seems good to him that he is
tranquilito que le parece bien que esté
calm but that the things they
tranquilito pero que las cosas que
did in the past were worthy of being
hacían en el pasado era para pegarle un
shot and this as always doesn't lose them
tiro y esto como siempre no los pierde
always this is what always happens
siempre esto es lo que pasa siempre
when for example giving a video to
cuando por ejemplo darles un vídeo a
someone like Ibai the victimizer the other day
alguien como ibai victimario el otro día
when an invoice that there are many normal
cuando un factura que hay muchos normal
on twitter and on social networks they
en twitter y en las redes sociales que
start saying like that or that Dallas is
empiezan a decir como que o que dallas
already looking for controversy that he does it
ya está buscando polémica que lo hace
to gain followers that he does it for
para ganar seguidores que lo hace por
money it's on top of that the other one comes to
dinero está encima que viene el otro
touch him  balls with the things that
tocarle las pelotas con las cosas que ha
the kid has said on top of that he will not even be able to
dicho encima el chaval no podrá ni
respond no if they use arguments that
responder no si utilizan argumentos que
are really
son realmente
wheat michu and vai and now jordi white
wheat michu y vai y ahora jordi white
this dallas that here all when it
este dallas que aquí todas cuando a mí
seems to me that he has been too
me parece que ha sido demasiado
respectful comparing it with the things
respetuoso comparándolo con las cosas
that jordi while has said about him we are going to
que jordi while ha dicho de él lo vamos
do it oneto or rather we are going to compare the
a hacer oneto o sea vamos a comparar las
things that jordi while has said about him
cosas que jordi while ha dicho sobre él
in all the clicks that we have seen if you have not said
en todos los clics que hemos visto si no
it I will leave you in the
lo habéis dicho os dejaré en la
description the reaction to my video on the
descripción la reacción a mi vídeo en el
secondary channel so that you can see it
canal secundario para que lo veáis
compare the things that jordi gual has said
comparar las cosas que ha dicho jordi
about dallas with those that dallas
gual de dallas con las que dallas le
responded to him in this video compare it
respondió en este vídeo compararla por
please jordi galán has dedicated a
favor jordi galán se ha dedicado un
video to himself that he has fallen xd or how low he has
vídeo que bajó ha caído xd o qué bajo ha
fallen bullets for answering you no but
caído balas por responderte no pero
surely we are cool did not jordi tell him
seguro que estemos molo no le dijo jordi
how low he had fallen with dallas
lo bajo que había caído con dallas
when he said that in the past he would have
cuando dijo que en el pasado lo hubiera
shot him or when he said that dallas
pegado un tiro o cuando dijo que dallas
was all the things that he had said win
era todas las cosas que había dicho win
michu that you already know that all the things
michu que ya sabéis que todas las cosas
that win had done  bischoff on the
que había hecho win bischoff en la
subject that explains in a court like
materia que explica en un juzgado como
when jordi gual gains fame and you also
cuando jordi gual gana fama y tú también
want to pathetic here another one who
quieres patético aquí otro que le
answers dallas to a tweet if they are the
contesta a dallas a un tweet si ellos de
same better stay quiet don't mess with him
igual mejor quédate callado con el no te
okay don't mess with jordi whoever messes with whoever he
metás vale con jordi no te metas el que
wants but don't mess with him
se meta con quien quiera pero con el no
the day that dallas stops living
te metás el día que dallas deje de vivir
at the expense of others maybe he
a costa de otros puede ser que se
apologizes or they apologize to him
disculpe o se disculpen con él
do sul pal [ __ ] they are not going to apologize
do sul pal [__] no se van a disculpar
with the quiz there is no need to apologize he is not
con el quiz no hay que disculparse no se
going to apologize I was watching
va a disculpar estaba mirando el vídeo
dallas' video about jordi while and I have to
de dallas sobre jordi while y tengo que
say that they still seem more canelo to me
decir que todavía me parecen más canelo
because jordi has sent a nude to your
porque jordi le ha enviado nude a tu
partner and you eating your snot
pareja y tú comiéndote los mocos de
really if I were your friend I would feel
verdad si yo fuese tu amigo me daría
sorry for him he is on top of glorifying jordi
pena está encima vanagloriando a jordi
gual for having done that while the
gual por haber hecho eso mientras que la
girl is dallas' girlfriend well I am
chica es la novia de dallas bien yo
talking about now if what he decides is
hablo de ahora si lo que decide es
true that the complaint is made and not
verdad que se haga la denuncia y no
half hour videos monetized burn it
vídeos de media hora monetizado quema lo
asked for it  monetized careful you see win
pidió monetizado cuidado lo veis win
michu was right because he will not
michu tenía la razón porque él no
monetize and give like that and this tells
monetizará y dar así y esto le dice a
Vigile to file a complaint, they seem
vigile que se haga denuncia me parecen
totally pathetic to me also because on the
totalmente patético también porque por
one hand he says anac if he has something to
una parte dice anac si tiene algo que
say to file a complaint but then
decir que ponga una denuncia pero luego
on the other hand every time Dallas announces
por otra cada vez que dallas anunciase
someone the allies and this
anunciado a alguien los aliados y este
group of people who defend it they
grupo de gente que defiende es llevando
start saying that Dallas starts to
se ponen a decir que dallas se pone a
denounce everyone that he
denunciar a todo el mundo que es que
has a lot of free time and starts to
tiene mucho tiempo libre y se pone a
denounce because potato rubber Jordi
denunciar porque patata goma jordi le
is doing so well
está yendo tan bien
Dallas just remembered everything hahaha
dallas justo se acordó de todo jajaja
same with eBay well it's clean now it's
igual con ebay bueno está limpia ya se
finished justifying itself no what has been
le acabó de justificar no lo que ha sido
the trigger that Dallas
el detonante de que dallas
now has been the clicks have circulated in
ahora ha sido los clics han rulado en
recent days and now what many of us are
estos últimos días y ahora lo que muchos
waiting for is not to know how he is going to
estamos esperando no es saber cómo va a
respond and if
responder y si va a responder
Jordi while is going to respond there are several options I
jordi while existe varias opciones yo
think one of the most likely is that
creo que una de las más probables es que
Jordi while will do as he did and will go and
jordi while hagan como hizo y va a ir y
act like Dallas is only
hacer el papel como de que a dallas sólo
looking for controversy I don't  I'm going to answer
busca polémica yo no le voy a responder
because I'm on another level and not answering is
porque estoy a otro nivel y no contestar
completely ignoring the issue and trying to make
pasar absolutamente el tema e intentar
all of this remain in some kind
que todo esto queden como en una especie
of limbo and forgotten what happens is
de limbo y en el olvido lo que pasa de
clear this time it's not like the
claro en esta ocasión no es como el
video he made and vice this time there
vídeo que él hizo y vice en esta ocasión
are some accusations that are quite
hay algunas acusaciones que son bastante
strong that are quite relevant
fuertes que son bastante relevantes en
against Jordi wild and I think he
contra de jordi wild y yo creo que
should give some kind of explanation
debería dar algún tipo de explicación
another option would be for Jordi to acknowledge
otra opción sería que jordi reconozca
things and apologize for everyone and the one I think
las cosas y se disculpe por todos y la
could happen I don't know if I'm
que yo creo que podría pasar no sé si me
going to be wrong but maybe I'm going to
voy a equivocar pero a lo mejor voy a
have too much confidence in him and I
tener demasiada confianza en él y yo
think Jordi is going to respond by
creo que jordi va a responder pidiéndole
apologizing to Dallas for the things he's
disculpas a dallas por las cosas que le
said in the past I think Jordi is going to
ha dicho en el pasado yo creo que jordi
be enough of a gentleman because
va a ser lo suficiente caballero porque
he knows that all the things that have been
él sabe que todas las cosas que se han
said about him are false I already explained to you in
dicho de él son falsas ya le expliqué en
the reaction I made you
la reacción que hice
don't have to like Dallas well
dallas no tiene por qué caerte bien
repellent unpleasant that you don't like
repelente desagradable que no te gusten
his criticism that you don't like his
sus críticas que no te guste su
ideology that you don't agree with his
ideología que no estés de acuerdo con su
argument but one thing is all of that is
argumento pero una cosa es todo eso es
totally  legal and another thing is that you
totalmente lícito y otra cosa es que tú
believe that he is a pedophile jumper a
creas que sea un pedófilo saltador un
stalker you may not like him but
acosador a ti puede caerte mal pero
to recognize that he did not profile and all those
reconocer que no se perfiló y todas esas
things is not incompatible or rather the fact that
cosas no es incompatible o sea el hecho
you defend that everything that has been
de que tú defiendas que todo lo que se
said about this kid is false does not
ha dicho de este chaval es falso no
imply that I am saying that you like
implica que esté diciendo que te cae
this yes I think that Jordi I am going to
bien esto sí yo creo que jordi voy a
trust him I do not know if I am going to be
confiar en él no sé si me voy a
wrong but considering that he is a kid
equivocar pero pensando que es un chaval
who is a year older than me who is
que tiene un año más que yo que se
supposed to reason things out and
supone que tiene que razonar las cosas y
be a little tougher even though in the past he has
ser un poco más duro aunque en el pasado
not been I think that we all make
no lo haya sido yo creo que todos nos
mistakes and I want to trust that
equivocamos y yo quiero confiar en que
Jordi is going to recognize that he went too far
jordi va a reconocer que se ha pasado
with Dallas, that he was wrong and that
con dallas que se ha equivocado y que
all the things that have been said about him
todas las cosas que se ha dicho de él
are not true and apologize
pues que no son ciertas y disculparse
for those kinds of threats maybe he will
por esa especie de amenazas quizá él va
say that they were jokes or something like that
a decir que fueron bromas o algo por el
but I think he deserves an
estilo pero creo que se merece una
apology and I think that about the photos of
disculpa y creo que lo de las fotos a
Mieres is what Dallas has said and about
mieres está que ha contado dallas y lo
the conversations with the other girl I think
de las conversaciones con la otra chica
What he will do is probably justify it
creo que lo que hará será justificarlo
by saying that they were joking conversations,
a decir que eran conversaciones de broma
that he is always so affectionate with people
que él es así de cariñoso con la gente
because he didn't know how old she
siempre porque no sabía la edad que
was, although he didn't know if she had a boyfriend or
tenía aunque no sabía si tenía novio o
something like that, and nothing, guys, what it would be, I
algo así y nada chavales lo que sería
will surely be commenting on it, so
seguramente lo estaré comentando así que
please subscribe to this channel, give it a
por favor suscribiros a este canal darle
like if you liked it, and we'll see the
like si os ha gustado y los vemos el
next video.
siguiente vídeo